Is it a trick
这是一个把戏吗
I think I can do that
我想我能做到
Does cracking on the side
侧面开裂吗
Separate the yolk
分离蛋黄
How is broken
怎么破
Listen to garbage
听垃圾
Kobe
What's that yoke
那是什么
It's weird
有点奇怪
Wow this is so f******
哇，好厉害
Is pretty easy
很简单
Crackerjack play
饼干
I'm gonna trade back and forth here
我要在这里来回交易
I putting the baby inside the shell
我把蛋黄放在壳里
This is doing it for me
这是为我做的
Right
对
I actually don't think
我其实不认为
So the first thing when you're cracking an egg you should be doing it
因此，当您要打碎鸡蛋时，第一件事应该是做
What service is opposed to a sharp surface because that's going to keep you from getting the shell
什么服务与锋利的表面相对立，因为这将使您无法获得外壳
And I always separate between my fingers
我总是手指分开
This is primarily because the show has sharp edges so my fingers are less likely to Wake Me Up
这主要是因为该节目具有锐利的边缘，所以我的手指不太可能唤醒我
What that is
那是什么